Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: N-Se, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 5:1-276)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:103)
      - Correspondence from H. Abby Penrose, New York, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:104)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. R. Pepper, Bristol, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:105)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Pepsodent Company, Chicago, Illinois, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:106)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Robert Perkins, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:107)
      - Correspondence from Lizzie Fitzgerald Perkinson, Danville, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:108)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. W. Perryman, Norfolk, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:109)
      - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, Anti-Saloon League of Virginia, Richmond, Virginia, 1914-1929., 111 items. (Box-folder 5:110-116)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, March-April 1914., 11 items. (Box-folder 5:110)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, May-June 1914., 18 items. (Box-folder 5:111)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, July-October 1914., 22 items. (Box-folder 5:112)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, April 1918., 16 items. (Box-folder 5:113)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, May-June 1918., 17 items. (Box-folder 5:114)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, July-August 1918., 15 items. (Box-folder 5:115)
        - Correspondence with J. Sidney Peters, 1920-1929., 12 items. (Box-folder 5:116)
      - Duplicate correspondence to F. C. Peterson, University, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:117)
      - Correspondence from L. W. H. Peyton, Staunton, Virginia, 1922., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:118)
      - Duplicate correspondence from William R. Phelps, Bedford, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:119)
      - Correspondence to "Mr. Phillips," Richmond, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:120)
      - Correspondence from E. B. Phillips, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1912., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:121)
      - Correspondence from E. R. Phillips, Miona, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:122)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Harry D. Phillips, Melfa, Virginia, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:123)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. Lee Phillips, Norfolk, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:124)
      - Correspondence from John Lloyd Phillips, Staunton, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:125)
      - Correspondence from J. L. Phillips, Linden, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:126)
      - Correspondence from L. T. Phillips, Melfa, Virginia, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:127)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Phillips Thompson Co., Wilmington, Virginia, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:128)
      - Correspondence from Lula Phillips, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:129)
      - Correspondence from D. S. Phlegar, Norfolk, Virginia, 1910, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:130)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George Pickett, Alexandria, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:131)
      - Telegrams to M. E. Pidgeon, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:132)
      - Copy of telegram to Walter B. Pitkin, New York City, New York, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:133)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. E. Pleasants, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:134)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Garland Pollard, Governor of Virginia, 1930-1934, 1914-1932., 18 items. (Box-folder 5:135)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Fitzhugh Lee Pollitt, Camden, New Jersey, 1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:136)
      - Correspondence from D. Porter, Richmond, Virginia, 1921., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:137)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. T. Porter, Saxis, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:138)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John Porter, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:139)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Rose Porter, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:140)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Postmaster of Norfolk, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:141)
      - Correspondence from Annie L. Potter, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:142A)
      - Correspondence from H. E. Potter, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1930., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:142B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. S. Potts, Easton, Maryland, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:143)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. H. Potts, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:144)
      - Correspondence from Bernard B. Powell, Franklin City, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:145)
      - Correspondence from E. H. Powell, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:146)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George H. Powell, Onancock, Virginia, 1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:147)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Henry Powell, Onancock, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:148)
      - Correspondence from J. T. Powell, Washington, D.C., 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:149)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Louis F. Powell, Richmond, Virginia, 1928-1929., 8 items. (Box-folder 5:150)
      - Duplicate correspondence to M. J. Powell, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:151)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. Fulton Powell, Berlin, Maryland, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:152)
      - Correspondence from S. P. Powell, Spotsylvania, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:153)
      - Correspondence from S. T. Powell, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:154A)
      - Correspondence from Stewart K. Powell, Onancock, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:154B)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas E. Powell, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1924., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:155)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Wesley T. Powell, Nassawaddox, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:156)
      - Correspondence from Richard T. Pratt, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:157)
      - Correspondence from H. L. [Price?], Blacksburg, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:158)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James H. Price, Richmond, Virginia, 1929, 1935., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:159)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. M. Prichard, Staunton, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:160)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. L. Prince, University of Richmond, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:161)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Princess Anne Circuit Court Clerk, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:162)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John L. Proffitt, Richmond, Virginia, 1927., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:163)
      - Duplicate correspondence to F. G. Provost, New York City, New York, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:164)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. S. Pruitt, Franklin City, Virginia, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:165)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Victoria Pruitt, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1924-1935., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:166)
      - Correspondence from W. H. Pruitt, Temperanceville and Accomac, Virginia, 1911, 1927., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:167)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. R. Pugh, Elk Creek, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:168)
      - Correspondence from L. E. Pugh, Newport News, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:169)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charles W. Purnell, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:170)
      - Correspondence from George W. Purnell, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1909., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:171)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Oscar M. Purnell, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:172)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. J. Purse, Detroit, Michigan, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:173)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Harvey C. Pusey, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:174)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Lloyd Pusey, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1930., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:175)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mary Belle Pusey, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:176)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Quality Press, Richmond, Virginia, 1925-1927., 6 items. (Box-folder 5:177)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. and Mrs. A. G. Quarles, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:178)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Thomas B. Quinby, Tampa, Florida, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:179)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. L. C. Quinn, Crisfield, Maryland, 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:180)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John J. Raskob, New York City, New York, 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:181)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Joe Rasnick, St. Paul, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:182)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Russell Rawlings, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:183)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John L. Rayfield, Mappsville, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:184)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. Virginia Rayfield, Newport News, Virginia, 1900., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:185)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. H. Revell, Onley, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:186)
      - Correspondence from M. W. Revere, Wake, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:187)
      - Correspondence from C. J. Rew, Parksley, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:188)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John and William Rew, Los Angeles, California, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:189)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mary Rew, Parksley, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:190)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with L. R. Reynolds, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:191)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. W. Reynold, Marianville, Virginia, 1914, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:192)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Luther Rice, Reedville, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:193)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rice's Fashion Corner, Norfolk, Virginia, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:194)
      - Correspondence from Albert A. Richards, Accomac, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:195)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Clayton T. Richardson, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:196)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rev. Ed J. Richardson, Richmond, Virginia, 1914-1935., 14 items. (Box-folder 5:197)
      - Correspondence from Homer Richey, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:198)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with the Richmond News Leader, 1918-1921., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:199A)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Richmond, Times Dispatch, 1928-1935., 10 items. (Box-folder 5:199B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Richmond Virginian, 1914., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:200)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Rev. Roland Riddick, Franktown, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:201)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with M. C. Riggs, Hopeton, Virginia, 1925., 2 item. (Box-folder 5:202)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Samuel T. Riley, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:203)
      - Correspondence from Bettie S. Roberts, Salisbury, Maryland, 1911., 7 items. (Box-folder 5:204)
      - Telegram from Edward C. Roberts, Exmore, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:205)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Henry Roberts, Bristol, Virginia, 1925, 1929., 7 items. (Box-folder 5:206)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Hugh S. Roberts, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1935., 1 item (Box-folder 5:207)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. Stuart Robertson, Orange, Virginia, 1935., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:208)
      - Correspondence from R. H. Robertson, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1909., 6 items. (Box-folder 5:209)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Judge Thomas B. Robertson, Hopewell, Virginia, 1924-1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:210)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. Willis Robertson [A. Willis Robertson?], Lexington, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:211)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George B. Robey, Fairfax, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:212)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Archibald C. Robinson, Richmond, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:213)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. Lee Robinson, Newport News, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:214)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with V. D. L. Robinson, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:215)
      - Correspondence from David C. Rockwell, Chicago, Illinois, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:216)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. R. Rogers, Director of the Yorktown Sesquicentennial Commission, Yorktown, Virginia, 1931., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:217)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Carroll A. Rogers, Craddockville, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:218)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence to John H. Rogers, Norfolk, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:219)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Paul Rogers, Nassawadox, Virginia, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:220)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Samuel Rogers, Petersburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:221)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Spencer F. Rogers, Onancock, Virginia, 1915, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:222)
      - Correspondence from Grace Rohleder, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:223)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Daniel C. Roper, Washington, D.C., 1919-1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:224)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. T. Ross, Accomac, Virginia, 1920., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:225)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William Ross, Accomac, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:226A)
      - Correspondence from A. P. Rowe, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:226B)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. E. Rowe, Fox Hill, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:227)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. M. Rowland, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:228)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. T. Roweley, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:229)
      - Correspondence from W. W. Royall, Jefferson, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:230)
      - Correspondence from H. P. B. Rue, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1910., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:231)
      - Correspondence from Fred E. Ruediger, Accomac, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:232)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Edward M. Rulon, Exmore, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:233)
      - Correspondence from S. H. Rupp, Roanoke, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:234)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charles F. Russell, Greenbush, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:235)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. F. Russell, Mearsville, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:236)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Robert A. Russell, Rustburg, Virginia, 1923., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:237)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Stuart Russell, Parksley, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:238)
      - Correspondence from Garrett Ryland, Richmond, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:239)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Christopher St. Clair, Crisfield, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:240)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. B. St. Martin, Gates City, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:241)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas J. Sanderlin, Richmond, Virginia, 1925, 1929., 5 items. (Box-folder 5:242)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William B. Sanders, White Stone, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:243)
      - Correspondence from S. M. Sanderson, Petersburg, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:244)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Oliver J. Sands, Richmond, Virginia, 1924., 10 items. (Box-folder 5:245)
      - Correspondence from Lee Satchell, Makemie Park, Virginia, 1915., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:246)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John and Elizabeth Saul, Salem, Virginia, 1931-1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:247)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John R. Saunders, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 16 items. (Box-folder 5:248)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Jon R. Saunders, Richmond, Virginia, 1912-1922., 16 items. (Box-folder 5:249)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Peter Saunders, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:250)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. S. Saunders, Exmore, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:251)
      - Duplicate correspondence to B. P. Savage, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:252)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. S. Savage, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:253)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Fred Savage, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1931-1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:254)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Herbert Miles Savage, Modest Town, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:255)
      - Correspondence from I. Henry Savage, Chicoteague, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:256)
      - Correspondence from J. B. Savage, Weirwood, Virginia, n.d., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:257)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Joseph L. Savage, Painter, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:258)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. Lloyd Savage, Onley, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:259)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Sadie Savage, Onley, Virginia, 1922-1933., 10 items. (Box-folder 5:260)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Gordon M. Scarborough, Carson, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:261)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Gordon M. Scarborough, Carson, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:262)
      - Correspondence from Annie M. Schmolz, New York City, New York, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:263)
      - Correspondence from F. X. Schuller, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:264)
      - Correspondence from E. Thomas Scott, Norfolk, Virginia, [1920]., 2 items. (Box-folder 5:265)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Jewell Riley Scott, Onancock, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:266)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John C. Scott, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:267)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Julia Frances Scott, Parksley, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:268)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lotta Scott, Onancock, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:269)
      - Telegram from Dr. S. L. Scott, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:270)
      - Correspondence from W. A. Scott, Harborton, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:271)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Woodie Scott, Capeville, Virginia, [1911]., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:272)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Sears and Roebuck, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:273)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Secretary of Commerce, Washington, D.C., 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:274)
      - Correspondence from R. B. Segar, Saluda, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:275)
      - Correspondence from R. E. Selby, Greenbackville, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:276)
    - General Correspondence: Sh-Wh, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 6:1-275)
      - Correspondence from V. R. Schackleford, Orange, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:1)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Arthur B. Sharpe, Richmond, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:2)
      - Correspondence from John S. Sharpley, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1910., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:3)
      - Duplicate correspondence to S. J. Shelbourne, Pennington Gap, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:4)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Alma Shelhorse, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:5)
      - Duplicate correspondence to B. Morgan Shepherd, Richmond, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:6)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Hugh D. Shepherd, Sr., 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:7)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lillian A. Shepherd, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:8)
      - Correspondence from J. L. Sherrand, Richmond, Virginia, 1920-1923., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:9)
      - Duplicate correspondence to "The Sherwood," Old Point, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:10)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John M. Shields, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:11)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. G. Shirley, State Highway Commissioner, Richmond, Virginia, 1930-1934., 5 items. (Box-folder 6:12)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Cdr. M. C. Shirley, Norfolk Naval Base, Norfolk, Virginia, 1931-1933., 5 items. (Box-folder 6:13)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William T. Shrieves, Onley, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:14)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Amos Shryock, Winchester, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:15)
      - Correspondence from J. Milton Shue, Goochland, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:16)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Robert W. Shultice, Norfolk, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:17)
      - Correspondence from S. C. Siloesthan, Hopkins, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:18)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Georgianna Wray Sinclair, Roanoke, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:19)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. J. Singleton, Mappsville, Virginia, 1910., 10 items. (Box-folder 6:20)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lena E. Smethie, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:21)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. C. Smith, Lynnhaven and Norfolk, Virginia, [1911], 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:22)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Blackburn Smith, Berryville, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:23)
      - Correspondence from E. Hugh Smith, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:24)
      - Correspondence from E. Sumter Smith, Bedford City, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:25)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Edgar J. Smith, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1924, 1927., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:26)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Edwin J. Smith, Norfolk, Virginia, 1911-1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:27)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Francis S. Key Smith, Washington, D.C., 1931-1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:28)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Francis W. Smith, Laster Manor, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:29)
      - Correspondence from George L. Smith, Tabb, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:30)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Harry B. Smith, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 4 items. (Box-folder 6:31)
      - Correspondence from J. H. Smith, Capeville, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:32)
      - Correspondence from Joseph H. Smith, Petersburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:33)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lemuel Smith, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:34)